radley.co.uk 2019-06-29

# Privacy & Cookie Policy

## Privacy Policy

**INTRODUCTION**   

Welcome to the Radley + Co Limited privacy notice.

Radley + Co respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal data. This privacy notice will inform you as to how we look after your personal data when you visit our website (regardless of where you visit it from) or when you visit any of our stores and tell you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you.

This privacy notice is provided in a layered format so you can click through to the specific areas set out below.  Please also use the Glossary at the back of the notice to understand the meaning of some of the terms used in this privacy notice.

**1\. [ _IMPORTANT INFORMATION AND WHO WE ARE_ ]**

**2\. [ _THE DATA WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU_ ]**

**3\. [ _HOW IS YOUR PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED_ ]**

**4\. [ _HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA_ ]**

**5\. [ _DISCLOSURES OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA_ ]**

**6\. [ _INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS_ ]**

**7\. [ _DATA SECURITY_ ]**

**8\. [ _DATA RETENTION_ ]**

**9\. [ _YOUR LEGAL RIGHTS_ ]**

**10\. [ _GLOSSARY_ ]** ****

**1.**    **IMPORTANT INFORMATION AND WHO WE ARE**   

**PURPOSE OF THIS PRIVACY NOTICE**   

This privacy notice aims to give you information on how Radley + Co collects and processes your personal data through your use of our website, your use of our stores, or your participation in a Radley + Co event, including any data you may provide when you sign up to our newsletter, purchase a product or service or take part in a competition.

This website is not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children.

**CONTROLLER**   

Radley + Co Limited is the controller and responsible for your personal data (referred to as “Radley + Co”, “we”, “us” or “our” in this privacy notice).

We have appointed a Data Privacy Manager who is responsible for overseeing questions in relation to this privacy notice. If you have any questions about this privacy notice, including any requests to exercise your legal rights, please contact the Data Privacy Manager using the details set out below.

**CONTACT DETAILS   **

You can contact our Data Privacy Manager at:

_Post:_  
Radley + Co Limited   
3rd Floor,   
McBeath House,   
310 Goswell Road,   
London, EC1V 7LW  
FAO: Data Privacy Manager

Email:     dataprivacy@radleyandco.com

You have the right to make a complaint at any time to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues ([www.ico.org.uk](https://www.ico.org.uk/)). We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with your concerns before you approach the ICO so please contact us in the first instance.

**CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY NOTICE AND YOUR DUTY TO INFORM US OF CHANGES   **

This version was last updated on 3 May 2018 and historic versions can be obtained by contacting us.

It is important that the personal data we hold about you is accurate and current. Please keep us informed if your personal data changes during your relationship with us.

**THIRD-PARTY LINKS   **

This website may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements. When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy notice of every website you visit.

**2.**    **THE DATA WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU**   

Personal data, or personal information, means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified. It does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data).

We may collect, use, store and transfer different kinds of personal data about you which we have grouped together follows:

  1. **Identity Data** includes first name, maiden name, last name, username or similar identifier, marital status, title, date of birth and gender, and social media account names. 
  2. **Contact Data** includes billing address, delivery address, email address, telephone numbers.
  3. **Financial Data** includes bank account details.
  4. **Transaction Data** includes details about payments to and from you and other details of products and services you have purchased from us.
  5. **Technical Data** includes internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this website.
  6. **Profile Data** includes **** your username and password, purchases or orders made by you, your interests, preferences, feedback and survey responses.
  7. **Usage Data** includes information about how you use our website, products and services.
  8. **Marketing and Communications Data** includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and your communication preferences.

We also collect, use and share **Aggregated Data** such as statistical or demographic data for any purpose. Aggregated Data may be derived from your personal data but is not considered personal data in law as this data does **not** directly or indirectly reveal your identity. For example, we may aggregate your Usage Data to calculate the percentage of users accessing a specific website feature. However, if we combine or connect Aggregated Data with your personal data so that it can directly or indirectly identify you, we treat the combined data as personal data which will be used in accordance with this **privacy notice**.

We do not collect any **Special Categories of Personal Data** about you (this includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data). Nor do we collect any information about criminal convictions and offences.

**IF YOU FAIL TO PROVIDE PERSONAL DATA**     
Where we need to collect personal data by law, or under the terms of a contract we have with you and you fail to provide that data when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract we have or are trying to enter into with you (for example, to provide you with goods or services). In this case, we may have to cancel a product or service you have with us but we will notify you if this is the case at the time.  
**PHISHING**  
Phishing is the practice of tricking someone into giving confidential information. Examples include falsely claiming to be a legitimate company when sending an email to a user, in an attempt to get the user to send private information that will be used for identity theft and fraud.  
Radley will never ask you to send any personal details via email. If we require such details, for security reasons we will ask you to contact us by telephone. Should you receive an email claiming to be from Radley & Co requesting this kind of information please do not respond but contact us immediately.

**3.**    **HOW IS YOUR PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED?**   

We use different methods to collect data from and about you including through:

  1. **Direct interactions.** You may give us your Identity, Contact and Financial Data by filling in forms or by corresponding with us by post, phone, email or otherwise. This includes personal data you provide when you:
  2. Buy or express an interest in our products or services, in-store or on our website;
  3. create an account on our website;
  4. subscribe to our newsletter;
  5. request that we send marketing materials to you;
  6. enter a competition, promotion or survey;
  7. take part in a Radley + Co event;
  8. submit a product review;
  9. speak to customer services.
  10. **Automated technologies or interactions.** As you interact with our website and the emails we send to you, we may automatically collect Technical Data about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns. We collect this personal data by using cookies, server logs and other similar technologies. We may also receive Technical Data about you if you visit other websites employing our cookies. Please see our IP Addresses and Cookies policy for more details. 

**4.**    **HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA**   

We will only use your personal data when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal data in the following circumstances:

  1. Where we need to perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you.
  2. Where we have your consent. 
  3. Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests.
  4. Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.

You have the right to withdraw consent to marketing at any time by unsubscribing via the link provided with each marketing email we send to your or by contacting us on dataprivacy@radleyandco.com

**PURPOSES FOR WHICH WE WILL USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA**   

We have set out below, in a table format, a description of all the ways we plan to use your personal data, and which of the legal bases we rely on to do so. We have also identified what our legitimate interests are where appropriate.

Note that we may process your personal data for more than one lawful ground depending on the specific purpose for which we are using your data. Please contact us if you need details about the specific legal ground we are relying on to process your personal data where more than one ground has been set out in the table below.

**Purpose/Activity**

| 

**Type of data**

| 

**Lawful basis for processing including basis of legitimate interest**  
  
---|---|---  
  
To register you as a new customer

| 

(a) Identity  
(b) Contact

| 

Performance of a contract with you  
  
To process and deliver your order including:  
(a) Manage payments, fees and charges  
(b) Collect and recover money owed to us

| 

(a) Identity  
(b) Contact  
(c) Financial  
(d) Transaction  
(e) Marketing and Communications

| 

(a) Performance of a contract with you  
(b) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to recover debts due to us)  
  
|  |   
  
To manage our relationship with you which will include:  
(a) Notifying you about changes to our terms or privacy notice  
(b) Asking you to leave a review or take a survey

| 

(a) Identity  
(b) Contact  
(c) Profile  
(d) Marketing and Communications

| 

(a) Performance of a contract with you  
(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation  
(c) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated and to study how customers use our products/services)  
  
To enable you to partake in an event, prize draw, competition or complete a survey

| 

(a) Identity  
(b) Contact  
(c) Profile  
(d) Usage  
(e) Marketing and Communications

| 

(a) Performance of a contract with you  
(b) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them and grow our business)  
(c) Consent  
  
To administer and protect our business and this website (including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data)

| 

(a) Identity  
(b) Contact  
(c) Technical

| 

(a) Necessary for our legitimate interests (for running our business, provision of administration and IT services, network security, to prevent fraud and in the context of a business reorganisation or group restructuring exercise)  
(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation  
  
To deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you

| 

(a) Identity  
(b) Contact  
(c) Profile  
(d) Usage  
(e) Marketing and Communications  
(f) Technical

| 

Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them, to grow our business and to inform our marketing strategy)  
  
To use data analytics to improve our website, products/services, marketing, customer relationships and experiences

| 

(a) Technical  
(b) Usage

| 

Necessary for our legitimate interests (to define types of customers for our products and services, to keep our website updated and relevant, to develop our business and to inform our marketing strategy)  
  
To make suggestions and recommendations to you about goods or services that may be of interest to you

| 

(a) Identity  
(b) Contact  
(c) Technical  
(d) Usage  
(e) Profile

| 

  1. Necessary for our legitimate interests (to develop our products/services and grow our business); or
  2. Consent

**MARKETING**   

We strive to provide you with choices regarding certain personal data uses, particularly around marketing and advertising.  An online customer can update their personal data and choices in the “My Account” section of our website.  Customers without an online profile may update their choices either by calling Customer Care on +44(0) 207 741 1055 or visiting one of our stores. 

**PROMOTIONAL OFFERS FROM US**   

We may use your Identity, Contact, Technical, Usage and Profile Data to form a view on what we think you may want or need, or what may be of interest to you. This is how we decide which products, services and offers may be relevant for you (this is “marketing”).

You will receive marketing communications from us if you have requested information from us or purchased goods or services from us and, in each case, you have not opted out of receiving that marketing. You will also receive marketing communications from us if you have provided us with your details when you entered a competition or registered for a promotion and gave us your consent as part of that process. 

**THIRD-PARTY MARKETING**     
We will get your express opt-in consent before we share your personal data with any other company for marketing purposes.

**OPTING OUT**   

You can ask us or third parties to stop sending you marketing messages at any time by logging into the website and checking or unchecking relevant boxes to adjust your marketing preferences or by following the opt-out links on any marketing message sent to you or by contacting us.

Opting out of marketing messages will not prevent you receiving non-marketing messages from us, for example relating to products ordered from us, responses to customer service queries etc.

**COOKIES**   

You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when websites set or access cookies. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this website may become inaccessible or not function properly. For more information about the cookies we use, please see our IP Addresses and Cookies policy for more details.

**CHANGE OF PURPOSE**   

We will only use your personal data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. If you wish to get an explanation as to how the processing for the new purpose is compatible with the original purpose, please contact us.

If we need to use your personal data for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and we will explain the legal basis which allows us to do so.

Please note that we may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent, in compliance with the above rules, where this is required or permitted by law.

**5.**    **DISCLOSURES OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA**   

We may have to share your personal data with the parties set out below for the purposes set out in the table in paragraph 4 above.

  1. External Third Parties as set out in the _Glossary_.
  2. Third parties to whom we may choose to sell, transfer, or merge parts of our business or our assets. Alternatively, we may seek to acquire other businesses or merge with them. If a change happens to our business, then the new owners may use your personal data in the same way as set out in this privacy notice.

We require all third parties to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our third-party service providers to use your personal data for their own purposes and only permit them to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.

**6.**    **INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS**   

Some of our external third parties are based in Asia Pacific and the USA, outside the European Economic Area ( **EEA** ) so their processing of your personal data will involve a transfer of data outside the EEA.

Whenever we transfer your personal data out of the EEA, we ensure a similar degree of protection is afforded to it by ensuring at least one of the following safeguards is implemented:

  1. We will only transfer your personal data to countries that have been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection for personal data by the European Commission. For further details, see <https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/adequacy-protection-personal-data-non-eu-countries_en>
  2. Where we use certain service providers, we may use specific contracts approved by the European Commission which give personal data the same protection it has in Europe. For further details, see <https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/model-contracts-transfer-personal-data-third-countries_en>
  3. Where we use providers based in the US, we may transfer data to them if they are part of the Privacy Shield which requires them to provide similar protection to personal data shared between the Europe and the US. For further details, see <https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/eu-us-privacy-shield_en>

Please contact us if you want further information on the specific mechanism used by us when transferring your personal data out of the EEA.

**7.**    **DATA SECURITY**   

We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.

We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.

**8.**    **DATA RETENTION**   

**HOW LONG WILL YOU USE MY PERSONAL DATA FOR?**   

We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

By law we have to keep basic information about our customers (including Contact, Identity, Financial and Transaction Data) for six years after they cease being customers for tax purposes.  We also keep this basic information about our customers for up to seven years following your most recent purchase from us, to enable us to deal efficiently with any after-sales queries that you may have.  We keep customer profile information that you have indicated you are happy for us to have in order to keep you up to date regarding our products, services and events and will keep this information until such time as you indicate you no longer wish us to keep this data, or until a maximum of seven years following your most recent positive interaction with a marketing communication (e.g. clicking on a link in an email taking you to our website) – whichever of these two periods is shorter.

In some circumstances you can ask us to delete your data: see [ _Request erasure_ ] below for further information.

In some circumstances we may anonymise your personal data (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for research or statistical purposes in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.

**9.**    **YOUR LEGAL RIGHTS**   

Under certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data.

  1. [ _Request access to your personal data_ ].
  2. [ _Request correction of your personal data_ ].
  3. [ _Request erasure of your personal data_ ].
  4. [ _Object to processing of your personal data_ ].
  5. [ _Request restriction of processing your personal data_ ].
  6. [ _Right to opt-out of automated profiling of your personal data_ ]
  7. [ _Request transfer of your personal data_ ].
  8. [ _Right to withdraw consent_ ].

If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, please contact us.

**NO FEE USUALLY REQUIRED**   

You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.

**WHAT WE MAY NEED FROM YOU**   

We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal data (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response.

**TIME LIMIT TO RESPOND**   

We try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated.

**10.**    **GLOSSARY**   

**LAWFUL BASIS**   

**Legitimate Interest** means the interest of our business in conducting and managing our business to enable us to give you the best service/product and the best and most secure experience. We make sure we consider and balance any potential impact on you (both positive and negative) and your rights before we process your personal data for our legitimate interests. We do not use your personal data for activities where our interests are overridden by the impact on you (unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to by law). You can obtain further information about how we assess our legitimate interests against any potential impact on you in respect of specific activities by contacting us.

**Performance of Contract** means processing your data where it is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party or to take steps at your request before entering into such a contract.

**Comply with a legal or regulatory obligation** means processing your personal data where it is necessary for compliance with a legal or regulatory obligation that we are subject to.

**Consent** means you have explicitly given us permission to process your personal data.  In such circumstances we will have asked you a specific question and you will have entered information or ticked a tick-box to indicate your consent.

**THIRD PARTIES**   

**EXTERNAL THIRD PARTIES**   

  1. Service providers acting as processors based in the UK or EU who provide marketing, IT and system administration services.
  2. Professional advisers acting as processors or joint controllers including lawyers, bankers, auditors and insurers based in the UK and EU who provide consultancy, banking, legal, insurance and accounting services.
  3. HM Revenue & Customs, regulators and other authorities acting as processors or joint controllers based in the United Kingdom who require reporting of processing activities in certain circumstances.
  4. Customer service call, email, webchat, display advertising and website behavioural service providers, acting as processors, based in the UK, EU or USA;
  5. Social media platforms and service providers based in the USA 

**YOUR LEGAL RIGHTS**   

You have the right to:

     **Request access** to your personal data (commonly known as a “data subject access request”). This enables you to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.

     **Request correction** of the personal data that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate data we hold about you corrected, though we may need to verify the accuracy of the new data you provide to us.

     **Request erasure** of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal data where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your personal data where you have successfully exercised your right to object to processing (see below), where we may have processed your information unlawfully or where we are required to erase your personal data to comply with local law. Note, however, that we may not always be able to comply with your request of erasure for specific legal reasons which will be notified to you, if applicable, at the time of your request.

     **Object to processing** of your personal data where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground as you feel it impacts on your fundamental rights and freedoms. You also have the right to object where we are processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes. In some cases, we may demonstrate that we have compelling legitimate grounds to process your information which override your rights and freedoms.

     **Request restriction of processing** of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of your personal data in the following scenarios: (a) if you want us to establish the data’s accuracy; (b) where our use of the data is unlawful but you do not want us to erase it; (c) where you need us to hold the data even if we no longer require it as you need it to establish, exercise or defend legal claims; or (d) you have objected to our use of your data but we need to verify whether we have overriding legitimate grounds to use it.  In such circumstances we may reserve the right to delete your personal data rather than hold it but restrict processing, where our processes are not set up to enable a restriction.

     **Request the transfer** of your personal data to you or to a third party. We will provide to you, or a third party you have chosen, your personal data in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. Note that this right only applies to automated information which you initially provided consent for us to use or where we used the information to perform a contract with you.

**     Request to opt out of automated profiling** of your personal data.  You have the legal right to opt-out of any automated profiling of your personal data that could have a legal consequence for you, and have a human being involved in the processing decision rather than it being automated.  The only profiling of this type that we undertake is in our marketing activities, in which we tailor our marketing communications to your transactional history and product preferences.  If you wish to opt-out of this automated profiling please contact us, though please be aware that our systems are not configured to send un-tailored marketing communications to you, so in practice opting out of automated profiling will result in you being opted out of receiving marketing communications from us.

  **Withdraw consent at any time** where we are relying on consent to process your personal data. However, this will not affect the lawfulness of any processing carried out before you withdraw your consent. If you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide certain products or services to you. We will advise you if this is the case at the time you withdraw your consent.

## IP Addresses and Cookies

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us:  
To estimate our audience size and usage pattern.   
To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our site according to your individual interests.   
To speed up your searches.   
To recognise you when you return to our site. 

You may refuse to accept cookies by indicating that you do not consent to their use on the banner that appears on the homepage on your first visit. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site.Our cookies fall into fivecategories: 

**Strictly Necessary Cookies** \- These cookies enable services you have specifically asked for, they allow you to move around the website and use certain features, such as accessing secure pages.

**Session Cookies** – These cookies allow the site to ‘remember’ content from page to page for example shopping basket. These cookies expire when the user leaves the site or closes the browser. 

**Performance Cookies** \- These cookies collect information about how you use the website, for example pages you go to and any error messages you experience. These cookies don't gather information that identifies you, they are anonymous and help to improve how the website works.

**Functional Cookies** \- These cookies allow a website to remember choices you make, and tailor the website to provide enhanced content for you. 

**Targeting Cookies** \- These cookies are used to tailor marketing so it is relevant to you. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement. 

**Persistent cookies** \- This type of cookie is saved on your computer for a fixed period (usually a year or longer) and is not deleted when the browser is closed. Persistent cookies are used where we need to know who you are for more than one browsing session. For example, we use this type of cookie to store your preferences, so that they are remembered for the next visit.

We will use information held about you to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.

We may use your data to provide you, via email, post, telephone or SMS with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may be of interest to you, or share your details with selected third parties which we believe may be of interest to you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.We may use the data in accordance with the preferences expressed in your acceptance of the Radley cookie policy and terms and conditions of use of the Radley website.

Our [website/app] uses cookies/advertising IDs for the purpose of advertising. This enables us to show our advertisements to visitors who are interested in our products on partner websites and apps. Re-targeting technologies use your cookies or advertising IDs and display advertisements based on your past browsing behaviour. To read more and/or oppose to their services, please refer to their privacy policy here.

## Security

We realise how important it is to securely store any information that you provide us. The Radley transactional web site currently uses high-level Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology, the most advanced security software currently available for online transactions. You can therefore rest assured that we take the security of your payment and personal details very seriously. We may vary this in the future if we feel you will benefit from greater security whilst using our Website.

You can tell whether a webpage is secure as 'https' will replace the 'http' at the front of the [www.radley.co.uk](https://www.radley.co.uk/) in your browser address window, also a small locked padlock will appear in your browser window. 

## Phishing

Phishing is the practice of tricking someone into giving confidential information. Examples include falsely claiming to be a legitimate company when sending an email to a user, in an attempt to get the user to send private information that will be used for identity theft and fraud.

Radley will never ask you to send any personal details via email. If we require such details, for security reasons we will ask you to contact us by telephone. Should you receive an email claiming to be from Radley & Co requesting this kind of information please do not respond but contact us immediately. 

## Complaints

**If you feel that Radley is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact the**[Online Customer Service Department](https://www.radley.co.uk/contacts/) **or telephone +44 (0) 207 741 1055. You can also write to us at:-**  
**Radley & Co, McBeath House, 310 Goswell Road, London, EC1V 7LW**
